<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Spirituality on </title>
    <link>https://a.ngel.es/categories/spirituality/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Spirituality on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2017 Jose Angel Espinoza Portillo</copyright>
    <atom:link href="/categories/spirituality/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Lift</title>
      <link>https://a.ngel.es/post/lift/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2015 23:28:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://a.ngel.es/post/lift/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;embed video-player&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe 
    class=&#34;youtube-player&#34; 
    type=&#34;text/html&#34; 
    width=&#34;100%&#34; 
    height=&#34;400&#34; 
    src=&#34;http://www.youtube.com/embed/YAuqdPWTGLI&#34; 
    allowfullscreen 
    frameborder=&#34;0&#34;&gt;
  &lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;p&gt;A few years ago. When I was the Priesthood Quorum President in my local ward. I had the assignment of taking care of an special brother. He was in a bed all the time, he can hardly move, and his sickness could become a burden for most people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But embracing my calling in that moment, I managed to organice a regular visits. But it was really hard to manage the night visits, which includes cleaning his dippers and getting him comfy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For a little less of a year that was my work almost every day. Some days some other brother have already came before me, or if I was on a trip I ask other brother to do that job for me ( there was always a few really reliable brothers available to ask for this ).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was so used to work with that brother that he becomes more than a church brother, he was my friend, part of my family. And some day this beloved brother passed way. And he leave a great hole in my heart. My spiritual level drop so hard, that I could feel it, the quorum that I presided feels it. Eventually I was relieved from that calling.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now I&amp;rsquo;m much better and ready for new brothers to help.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
